<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Shawna Dean | Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://shawnadean.github.io/shawna-dean-portfolio/blogs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Shawna Dean | Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shawnadean.github.io/shawna-dean-portfolio/blogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Data-Driven Consulting: Combating food insecurity as a UF student</title>
      <link>https://shawnadean.github.io/shawna-dean-portfolio/blogs/ais-consulting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shawnadean.github.io/shawna-dean-portfolio/blogs/ais-consulting/</guid>
      <description>For the spring 2022 semester, the UF Association for Information Systems partnered with non-profit Smart North Florida to provide data visualization services to the University of North Florida Center for Nutrition and Food Security&amp;rsquo;s Hunger Network unit. I worked on a team of 4 to map various indicators of food insecurity in Duval County to identify strategies to improve and expand existing anti-hunger programs. Additionally, I took the initiative to compile our team&amp;rsquo;s findings into the report below: </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Credit Union Internship (Pt.1): No Experience to Exec-Level Dashboard </title>
      <link>https://shawnadean.github.io/shawna-dean-portfolio/blogs/credit-union1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shawnadean.github.io/shawna-dean-portfolio/blogs/credit-union1/</guid>
      <description>Read Time: 4 minutes
Article Summary: I was tasked with creating a dashboard to track cross functional initiatives starting from only a list of objectives and corresponding key results. I constructed a relational table and dashboard that enabled my audience to process a multitude of information in a few seconds. Related Article - My First Internship: Reducing processing time by 75%
In this story, I will describe
My Role at the Credit Union Building the Objectives and Key Results Dashboard What I Would Do Differently What I Learned My Role at the Credit Union Navy Federal Credit Union is the world’s largest credit union with 11.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Internship: Reducing processing time by 75% </title>
      <link>https://shawnadean.github.io/shawna-dean-portfolio/blogs/first-internship/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shawnadean.github.io/shawna-dean-portfolio/blogs/first-internship/</guid>
      <description>Read Time: 3 minutes
Article Summary: I was hired at a management consulting firm to assist with administrative duties. I took the self-initiative to create an Excel template that cut processing time from 20 to 5 minutes per report using nested functions and Power Query. I learned some basic principles of data analytics by addressing a business problem and being curious. Related Article - Credit Union Internship: No Experience to Exec-Level Dashboard In this story, I will cover</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Syntax</title>
      <link>https://shawnadean.github.io/shawna-dean-portfolio/blogs/markdown-syntax/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 23:29:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shawnadean.github.io/shawna-dean-portfolio/blogs/markdown-syntax/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;iframe-srchttpsdrivegooglecomdriveu0my-drive-width1000-height1250-aligncenteriframe&#34;&gt;&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://drive.google.com/drive/u/0/my-drive&#34; width=&#34;1000&#34; height=&#34;1250&#34; align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;embed-srccusersshawnadesktopcareershawna_dean_resume_8-2022-redactedpdf-width800px-height2100px-&#34;&gt;&lt;embed src=&#34;C:\Users\Shawna\Desktop\Career\Shawna_Dean_Resume_8-2022 redacted.pdf&#34; width=&#34;800px&#34; height=&#34;2100px&#34; /&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;iframe src=&#34;C:\Users\Shawna\Desktop\Career\Shawna_Dean_Resume_8-2022 redacted.pdf&#34; style=&#34;width: 100%;height: 100%;border: none;&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emoji Support</title>
      <link>https://shawnadean.github.io/shawna-dean-portfolio/blogs/emoji-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 22:53:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shawnadean.github.io/shawna-dean-portfolio/blogs/emoji-support/</guid>
      <description>Emoji can be enabled in a Hugo project in a number of ways. :zap:
Emoji Support The emojify function can be called directly in templates or Inline Shortcodes.
To enable emoji globally, set enableEmoji to true in your site’s configuration and then you can type emoji shorthand codes directly in content files; e.g.
The Emoji cheat sheet is a useful reference for emoji shorthand codes.
N.B. The above steps enable Unicode Standard emoji characters and sequences in Hugo, however the rendering of these glyphs depends on the browser and the platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Placeholder Text</title>
      <link>https://shawnadean.github.io/shawna-dean-portfolio/blogs/placeholder-text/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 22:41:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shawnadean.github.io/shawna-dean-portfolio/blogs/placeholder-text/</guid>
      <description>Lorem est tota propiore conpellat pectoribus de pectora summo.
Redit teque digerit hominumque toris verebor lumina non cervice subde tollit usus habet Arctonque, furores quas nec ferunt. Quoque montibus nunc caluere tempus inhospita parcite confusaque translucet patri vestro qui optatis lumine cognoscere flos nubis! Fronde ipsamque patulos Dryopen deorum.
Exierant elisi ambit vivere dedere Duce pollice Eris modo Spargitque ferrea quos palude Rursus nulli murmur; hastile inridet ut ab gravi sententia!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rich Content</title>
      <link>https://shawnadean.github.io/shawna-dean-portfolio/blogs/rich-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 19:53:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shawnadean.github.io/shawna-dean-portfolio/blogs/rich-content/</guid>
      <description>Hugo ships with several Built-in Shortcodes for rich content, along with a Privacy Config and a set of Simple Shortcodes that enable static and no-JS versions of various social media embeds.
Gist Simple Shortcode {{&amp;lt; gist spf13 7896402 &amp;#34;img.html&amp;#34; &amp;gt;}} Twitter Simple Shortcode {{&amp;lt; tweet GoHugoIO 1315233626070503424 &amp;gt;}} Profile is a customizable single-page portfolio theme for Hugo featuring a contact form and blog. Made by @gurusabarishh.https://t.co/KwYcwfdy16
&amp;mdash; GoHugo.io (@GoHugoIO) October 11, 2020 Vimeo Simple Shortcode {{&amp;lt; vimeo 146022717 &amp;gt;}} Youtube Simple Shortcode {{&amp;lt; youtube w7Ft2ymGmfc &amp;gt;}} </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
